<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<class name="PRIEST">
    <tree name="Discipline">
        <talent index="0" name="Ethereal Reach" icon="Absolution.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Dispel Magic, Cure Disease, Abolish Disease, Soul Quench, Power Word: Shield and Power Word: Fervor spells by 5 yards.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Dispel Magic, Cure Disease, Abolish Disease, Soul Quench, Power Word: Shield and Power Word: Fervor spells by 10 yards.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="1" name="Unbreakable Will" icon="MageArmor.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 3%.

Reduces the chance your spells will be dispelled by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 6%.

Reduces the chance your spells will be dispelled by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 9%.

Reduces the chance your spells will be dispelled by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 12%.

Reduces the chance your spells will be dispelled by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Fear, and Silence effects by an additional 15%.

Reduces the chance your spells will be dispelled by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Silent Resolve" icon="ManaRegenTotem.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 3%.

Reduces the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 6%.

Reduces the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 9%.

Reduces the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 30%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 12%.

Reduces the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 40%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces the threat generated by your spells by 15%.

Reduces the chance your helpful spells will be dispelled by 50%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Improved Power Word: Fortitude" icon="WordFortitude.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the effect of your Power Word: Fortitude and Prayer of Fortitude spells by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the effect of your Power Word: Fortitude and Prayer of Fortitude spells by 30%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Mental Focus" icon="MindMastery.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your total Intellect by 3%]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your total Intellect by 6%]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your total Intellect by 10%]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Meditation" icon="Sleep.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Allows 15% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Allows 30% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Allows 45% of your Mana regeneration to continue while casting.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Martyrdom" icon="Tranquility.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 50% chance to gain the Focused Casting effect that lasts for 6 sec after being the victim of a melee or ranged critical strike.  The Focused Casting effect prevents you from losing casting time when taking damage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 100% chance to gain the Focused Casting effect that lasts for 6 sec after being the victim of a melee or ranged critical strike.  The Focused Casting effect prevents you from losing casting time when taking damage.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Soul Quench (Rank 1)" icon="SoulQuench.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Heals a friendly target for 80-96.

This spell has a 50% increased critical effect chance on targets affected by Weakened Soul.

1.5 second cast.
35 Mana.  15 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Inner Focus" icon="WindWalkOn.png" requires="5">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[When activated, reduces the Mana cost of your next 4 spells by 50% and increases the spell's critical effect chance by 25% if the spell is capable of a critical effect.

2 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Spiritual Discipline" icon="Invisibilty.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Spirit by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Spirit by 6%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Spirit by 9%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your Spirit by 12%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your Spirit by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Mental Preparation" icon="FocusedPower.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Upon entering combat, causes the cooldowns of your next 2 spells to be reduced by 50% when triggered.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Upon entering combat, causes the cooldowns of your next 4 spells to be reduced by 50% when triggered.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Mending Shield" icon="MendingShield.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Power Word: Shield heals its target for 10% of their total Spirit every 3 secs. while it holds, and 20% of their Spirit if it gets dispelled.

Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Power Word: Shield heals its target for 20% of their total Spirit every 3 secs. while it holds, and 40% of their Spirit if it gets dispelled.

Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Power Word: Shield heals its target for 30% of their total Spirit every 3 secs. while it holds, and 60% of their Spirit if it gets dispelled.

Increases the damage absorbed by your Power Word: Shield by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="15" name="Reflective Shield" icon="ReflectiveShield.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Causes 8% of the damage you absorb with Power Word: Shield to be reflected back at the attacker.  This damage causes no threat.

When dispelled, your Power Word: Shield deals Holy damage equal to 40% of your total Spirit to the dispeller.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Causes 16% of the damage you absorb with Power Word: Shield to be reflected back at the attacker.  This damage causes no threat.

When dispelled, your Power Word: Shield deals Holy damage equal to 80% of your total Spirit to the dispeller.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Causes 24% of the damage you absorb with Power Word: Shield to be reflected back at the attacker.  This damage causes no threat.

When dispelled, your Power Word: Shield deals Holy damage equal to 120% of your total Spirit to the dispeller.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Causes 32% of the damage you absorb with Power Word: Shield to be reflected back at the attacker.  This damage causes no threat.

When dispelled, your Power Word: Shield deals Holy damage equal to 160% of your total Spirit to the dispeller.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Causes 40% of the damage you absorb with Power Word: Shield to be reflected back at the attacker.  This damage causes no threat.

When dispelled, your Power Word: Shield deals Holy damage equal to 200% of your total Spirit to the dispeller.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Improved Inner Fire" icon="InnerFire.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Inner Fire spell increases spell power by 10% of your total Spirit and reduces damage taken from physical critical strikes by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Inner Fire spell increases spell power by 20% of your total Spirit and reduces damage taken from physical critical strikes by 20%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Divine Spirit (Rank 1)" icon="DivineSpirit.png" requires="10">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Holy power infuses the target, increasing their Spirit by 17 for 30 min.

285 Mana.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="19" name="Strength of Will" icon="BlessedLife.png" requires="18">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Stamina by 5% and spell power by 10% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Stamina by 10% and spell power by 20% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="20" name="Improved Soul Quench" icon="ImpSoulQuench.png" requires="8">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Soul Quench spell by 0.5 seconds and the cooldown by 1 second.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Soul Quench spell by 1 second and the cooldown by 2 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Soul Quench spell by 1.5 seconds and the cooldown by 3 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Mental Agility" icon="MentalQuickness.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your instant cast spells a 50% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.5 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your instant cast spells a 100% chance to reduce the cast time of your next spell by 0.5 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Power Word: Fervor (Rank 1)" icon="PowerInfusion.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Kindles the inner fire of a party member's soul, increasing their spell power by up to 80.  Lasts 15 sec.  Affected by Weakened Soul.

210 Mana.  30 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="Holy">
        <talent index="1" name="Healing Focus" icon="HealingFocus.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 20% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage while casting any healing spell.

Increases your healing power by 15% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 40% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage while casting any healing spell.

Increases your healing power by 30% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives you a 60% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage while casting any healing spell.

Increases your healing power by 45% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives you a 80% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage while casting any healing spell.

Increases your healing power by 60% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives you a 100% chance to avoid interruption caused by damage while casting any healing spell.

Increases your healing power by 75% of your level.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Ward of Purity" icon="SpellWarding.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that protects you against Poison, removing 1 charge when a Poison effect hits you.  3 charges.  This effect is refreshed every 90 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that protects you against Poison, removing 1 charge when a Poison effect hits you.  3 charges.  This effect is refreshed every 75 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that protects you against Poison, removing 1 charge when a Poison effect hits you.  3 charges.  This effect is refreshed every 60 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that protects you against Poison, removing 1 charge when a Poison effect hits you.  3 charges.  This effect is refreshed every 45 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that protects you against Poison, removing 1 charge when a Poison effect hits you.  3 charges.  This effect is refreshed every 30 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Blessed Recovery" icon="BlessedRecovery.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[After being struck by a melee or ranged critical hit, heal 10% of the damage taken over 4 sec.  Additional critical hits taken during the effect increase the healing received.

Increases the amount healed by your Renew spell and Mending Shield effect by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[After being struck by a melee or ranged critical hit, heal 20% of the damage taken over 4 sec.  Additional critical hits taken during the effect increase the healing received.

Increases the amount healed by your Renew spell and Mending Shield effect by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[After being struck by a melee or ranged critical hit, heal 30% of the damage taken over 10 sec.  Additional critical hits taken during the effect increase the healing received.

Increases the amount healed by your Renew spell and Mending Shield effect by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Searing Light" icon="SearingLightPriest.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 2% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 4% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 4% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 8% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 6% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 12% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 8% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 16% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives your Smite and Holy Nova spells a 10% chance, and your Holy Fire spell a 20% chance, to disorient enemies for 2 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Holy Specialization" icon="Aspiration.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases the critical effect chance of your Holy spells by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Inspiration" icon="LayOnHands.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Restores 5 Rage, 10 Energy or 3% base Mana to the target after getting a critical effect from your healing spells and effects.  Only works if the target is in combat.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Restores 10 Rage, 20 Energy or 6% base Mana to the target after getting a critical effect from your healing spells and effects.  Only works if the target is in combat.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Revelation" icon="ImpHolyConcentration.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that increases the critical effect chance of your next spell, capable of a critical effect, by 100%.  This effect is refreshed every 90 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that increases the critical effect chance of your next spell, capable of a critical effect, by 100%.  This effect is refreshed every 60 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Holy Nova (Rank 1)" icon="HolyNova.png" requires="5">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Causes an explosion of holy light around the caster, causing 29 to 34 Holy damage to all enemy targets within 10 yards and healing all party members within 10 yards for 54 to 63.  These effects cause no threat.

185 Mana.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Holy Reach" icon="Purify.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Smite, Holy Fire and Resurrection spells and the radius of your Prayer of Healing, Holy Nova and Icon of Providence spells by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Smite, Holy Fire and Resurrection spells and the radius of your Prayer of Healing, Holy Nova and Icon of Providence spells by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Smite, Holy Fire and Resurrection spells and the radius of your Prayer of Healing, Holy Nova and Icon of Providence spells by 30%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Divine Fury" icon="SealOfWrath.png" requires="9">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Heal and Greater Heal spells by 0.1 sec.

Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova and Holy Fire spell by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Heal and Greater Heal spells by 0.2 sec.

Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova spell by 8%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Heal and Greater Heal spells by 0.3 sec.

Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova spell by 12%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Heal and Greater Heal spells by 0.4 sec.

Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova spell by 16%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Holy Fire, Heal and Greater Heal spells by 0.5 sec.

Reduces the Mana cost of your Holy Nova spell by 20%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Worship" icon="SealOfSalvation.png" requires="6">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.1 sec.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Flash Heal and Smite spells by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.2 sec.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Flash Heal and Smite spells by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.3 sec.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Flash Heal and Smite spells by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.4 sec.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Flash Heal and Smite spells by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces the casting time of your Smite, Prayer of Healing and Heal spells by 0.5 sec.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Flash Heal and Smite spells by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Radiant Guidance" icon="RadiantHealing.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Causing damage with Holy spells increases your healing power and Holy spell power by 1% of your total Spirit.  This effect stacks up to 15 times and lasts 15 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Causing damage with Holy spells increases your healing power and Holy spell power by 2% of your total Spirit.  This effect stacks up to 15 times and lasts 15 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Protector of the Flock" icon="DivineIllumination.png" requires="13">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a chance to gain the Protector of the Flock effect, whenever you or your party members within 40 yards take damage.

The Protector of the Flock effect reduces the cast time of your next Smite spell by 50% or the Mana cost of your next Holy Nova spell by 40%, or causes your next Holy Fire spell to increase the base Spirit of all party members by 50% for 10 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a chance to gain the Protector of the Flock effect, whenever you or your party members within 40 yards take damage.

The Protector of the Flock effect reduces the cast time of your next Smite spell by 100% or the Mana cost of your next Holy Nova spell by 80%, or causes your next Holy Fire spell to increase the base Spirit of all party members by 100% for 10 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Desperate Prayer" icon="DesperatePrayer.png" requires="14">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Instantly heals you for 546 to 654.

This spell has a 50% increased critical effect chance.

200 Mana.  5 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="19" name="Deliverance" icon="MoonGlow.png" requires="18">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[After your Health drops below 20%, reduces your chance to be hit with physical attacks by 25% and increases all resistances by 50% of your level.  Lasts 6 secs.  This effect can not occur more than once every 3 minutes.

Reduces the cast time of your Greater Heal spell by 0.2]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[After your Health drops below 20%, reduces your chance to be hit with physical attacks by 50% and increases all resistances by 100% of your level.  Lasts 6 secs.  This effect can not occur more than once every 3 minutes.

Reduces the cast time of your Greater Heal spell by 0.35]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[After your Health drops below 20%, reduces your chance to be hit with physical attacks by 75% and increases all resistances by 150% of your level.  Lasts 6 secs.  This effect can not occur more than once every 3 minutes.

Reduces the cast time of your Greater Heal spell by 0.5]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="21" name="Spiritual Guidance" icon="SpiritualGuidance.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases spell power by up to 5% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases spell power by up to 10% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases spell power by up to 15% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases spell power by up to 20% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases spell power by up to 25% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Icon of Providence (Rank 1)" icon="HolyProtection.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Summons an Icon of Providence with 600 health in front of the caster.  Prevents a party member within 20 yds of the Icon of Providence from dying, healing for 872 to 1033 when they take lethal damage.  Lasts 1 minute.

5 second cast.
650 Mana.  30 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="Shadow">
        <talent index="1" name="Shadow Affinity" icon="ShadowWard.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by 3%.

Your Fade spell reduces the chance to be hit with ranged attacks by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by 6%.

Your Fade spell reduces the chance to be hit with ranged attacks by 6%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by 9%.

Your Fade spell reduces the chance to be hit with ranged attacks by 9%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by 12%.

Your Fade spell reduces the chance to be hit with ranged attacks by 12%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by 15%.

Your Fade spell reduces the chance to be hit with ranged attacks by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Spirit Tap" icon="Requiem.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 2% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 10 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 4% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 10 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives you a 6% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 10 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives you a 8% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 10 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives you a 10% chance, when your Shadow spells deal damage, to gain a 100% bonus to your Spirit.  For the duration, your Mana will regenerate at a 50% rate while casting.  Lasts 10 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Blackout" icon="GatherShadows.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your Shadow damage spells a 2% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your Shadow damage spells a 4% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives your Shadow damage spells a 6% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives your Shadow damage spells a 8% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives your Shadow damage spells a 10% chance to stun the target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Improved Shadow Word: Pain" icon="ShadowWordPain.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 6 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the duration of your Shadow Word: Pain spell by 9 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Speed of Darkness" icon="Duality.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Shadow spells have a 5% chance to make your next non-Shadow spell with a cast time instant cast but cause 25% reduced healing or damage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Shadow spells have a 10% chance to make your next non-Shadow spell with a cast time instant cast but cause 25% reduced healing or damage.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Silence" icon="ImpPhaseShift.png" requires="4">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Silences the target, preventing them from casting spells for 5 sec.

This spell has a 50% chance of inflicting a Blackout effect on the target.

225 Mana.  60 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Psychic Aggression" icon="UnholyFrenzy.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 1 sec.

Reduces the cooldown of your Psychic Scream spell by 1.5 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 1.5 sec.

Reduces the cooldown of your Psychic Scream spell by 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the cooldown of your Mind Blast spell by 2 sec.

Reduces the cooldown of your Psychic Scream spell by 5 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Mind Flay (Rank 1)" icon="SiphonMana.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Assault the target's mind with Shadow energy, causing 75 Shadow damage over 3 sec and slowing their movement speed by 50%.

45 Mana.  3 second channel.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Shadow Reach" icon="ChillTouch.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 6% and your Mind Control spell by 2 yards.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 13% and your Mind Control spell by 4 yards.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the range of your Shadow damage spells by 20% and your Mind Control spell by 2 yards.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Shadow Focus" icon="BurningSpirit.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit with Shadow spells by 1%

Reduces the Mana cost and threat generated by your Shadow spells by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit with Shadow spells by 2%

Reduces the Mana cost and threat generated by your Shadow spells by 6%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit with Shadow spells by 3%

Reduces the Mana cost and threat generated by your Shadow spells by 9%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit with Shadow spells by 4%

Reduces the Mana cost and threat generated by your Shadow spells by 12%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit with Shadow spells by 5%

Reduces the Mana cost and threat generated by your Shadow spells by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Eldritch Covenant" icon="ConsumeMagic.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the Mana cost of your Shadow spells by 20%.

Casting Shadow damage spells cause you to take non-lethal Shadow damage equal to 5% of your base Health, increasing by 5% with each subsequent cast.  This effect resets after exiting combat or killing a target that yields experience or honor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the Mana cost of your Shadow spells by 35%.

Casting Shadow damage spells cause you to take non-lethal Shadow damage equal to 4% of your base Health, increasing by 4% with each subsequent cast.  This effect resets after exiting combat or killing a target that yields experience or honor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the Mana cost of your Shadow spells by 45%.

Casting Shadow damage spells cause you to take non-lethal Shadow damage equal to 3% of your base Health, increasing by 3% with each subsequent cast.  This effect resets after exiting combat or killing a target that yields experience or honor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces the Mana cost of your Shadow spells by 50%.

Casting Shadow damage spells cause you to take non-lethal Shadow damage equal to 2% of your base Health, increasing by 2% with each subsequent cast.  This effect resets after exiting combat or killing a target that yields experience or honor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces the Mana cost of your Shadow spells by 50%.

Casting Shadow damage spells cause you to take non-lethal Shadow damage equal to 1% of your base Health, increasing by 1% with each subsequent cast.  This effect resets after exiting combat or killing a target that yields experience or honor.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Improved Vampiric Embrace" icon="ImprovedVampiricEmbrace.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the damage your Shadow spells deal to targets by 8%, if they are below 20% Health and afflicted with Vampiric Embrace.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Vampiric Embrace's healing effect by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the damage your Shadow spells deal to targets by 15%, if they are below 20% Health and afflicted with Vampiric Embrace.

Increases the critical effect chance of your Vampiric Embrace's healing effect by 10%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Vampiric Embrace" icon="UnsummonBuilding.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Afflicts your target with Shadow energy that causes all party members to be healed for 15% of any Shadow spell damage you deal for 1 min.

6% base Mana.  10 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Shadow Weaving" icon="BlackPlague.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Shadow damage spells have a 20% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Shadow damage spells have a 40% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Shadow damage spells have a 60% chance to cause your target to be vulnerable to Shadow damage.  This vulnerability increases the Shadow damage dealt to your target by 3% and lasts 15 sec.  Stacks up to 5 times.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Dark Reflection" icon="Twilight (2).png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Shadow spell power by up to 8% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Shadow spell power by up to 16% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Shadow spell power by up to 24% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your Shadow spell power by up to 32% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your Shadow spell power by up to 40% of your total Spirit.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Shadowform" icon="Shadowform.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Assume a Shadowform, increasing your Shadow damage by 15% and reducing Physical damage done to you by 15%.  However, you may not cast Holy spells while in this form.

40% base Mana.  10 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <notes>
        <note index="0" name="General" icon="Book_11.png"><![CDATA[All Racials reworked.  (Except Devouring Plague)

Mana Burn - Now a Shadow skill with a cooldown of 10 secs.  Amount burned increased.

Power Word: Shield - Range reduced to 30 yards.]]></note>
        <note index="1" name="Clarifications" icon="Spy.png"><![CDATA[Priest base stats at level 60:

Health 1387
Mana 1436

STR 35
AGI 40
STAM 51
INT 119
SPI 127]]></note>
        <note index="5" name="(Undead) Touch of the Grave" icon="AnimateDead.png"><![CDATA[Slows the target by 40% for 10 seconds.  Only usable on targets below 20% health.]]></note>
        <note index="6" name="(Human) Flames of Abolition" icon="FireStarter.png"><![CDATA[When activated, reduces the cast time of your next Holy Fire spell by 1 second and increases its initial damage by 25%.  In addition, the damage over time effect will dispel 1 beneficial Magic effect from the target with each tick.

1 minute cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="7" name="(Human) Renewal of Faith (Final Rank)" icon="UnyieldingFaith.png"><![CDATA[Restores 400-1000 Mana plus your total Spirit.  Only usable when your Mana is below 20%.

5 minute cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="8" name="(Dwarf) Runeword: Fury of the Forge (Final Rank)" icon="SummonLightwell.png"><![CDATA[Inscribes a runeword of power at the targeted location that lasts 10 seconds, causing 192 to 215 Fire damage every 2 seconds to enemy targets inside its radius.

2 second cast.
10 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="9" name="(Dwarf) Runeword: Heart of the Mountain (Final Rank)" icon="EarthShock.png"><![CDATA[Inscribes a runeword of protection at the targeted location that lasts 20 seconds.  Party members inside its radius receive 1200 bonus armor and 50% increased resistance to Fear effects.

2 second cast.
1 minute cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="10" name="(Troll) Idol of the Loa (Final Rank)" icon="LoaIdol.png"><![CDATA[Summons an Idol of the Loa with 5 health in front of the caster. The Idol increases all attributes of party members within 30 yards by 25.  Lasts 2 minutes.

3 minute cooldown]]></note>
        <note index="11" name="(Troll) Blessing of the Cobra" icon="GuardianWard.png"><![CDATA[While active, reduces the global cooldown of all your spells by 0.5 sec and all healing done by 25%.

10 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="12" name="(Night Elf) Moon Glaive (Final Rank)" icon="UpgradeMoonGlaive.png"><![CDATA[Throws a glaive formed from moonlight, causing 335 to 380 Arcane damage to the target and bouncing to nearby enemy targets.  Bounces up to 2 times and deals 30% less damage each time.

2 second cast.]]></note>
        <note index="13" name="(Night Elf) Elune's Grace" icon="ElunesGrace.png"><![CDATA[Negates incoming Movement Impairing effects and increases your movement speed by 20% for 12 secs.

3 minute cooldown.]]></note>
    </notes>
</class>
