<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<class name="SECRET">
    <tree name="Tank (Custodianship)">
        <talent index="1" name="Deflection" icon="Parry.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Runic Fortification" icon="SpellWarding.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces spell pushback by 20% while channeling the Imprison spell.

Reduces the chance your spells are dispelled.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces spell pushback by 40% while channeling the Imprison spell.

Reduces the chance your spells are dispelled.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces spell pushback by 60% while channeling the Imprison spell.

Reduces the chance your spells are dispelled.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces spell pushback by 80% while channeling the Imprison spell.

Reduces the chance your spells are dispelled.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces spell pushback by 100% while channeling the Imprison spell.

Reduces the chance your spells are dispelled.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Runic Inscription: Shielding" icon="AvengersShield.png" requires="9">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Applies a Runic Inscription to your shield, increasing your block chance by 20% and armor gained from items by 100%.

When activated, grants you a protective shielding effect that absorbs damage equal to a percentage of your total armor.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Shield Proficiency" icon="ShieldGuard.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Allows you to use Shields to block damage.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Rune of Binding" icon="ChainsOfIce.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Casts a Rune, binding the target to you.  Causes the target to be knocked down for 2 secs. and forced to attack you for 4 secs. when the distance between you and the target becomes greater than 15 yards.  Lasts 30 secs.

1 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Improved Bolstering Rune-Circle" icon="Devotion.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Bolstering Rune-Circle reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by a percentage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Bolstering Rune-Circle reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by a percentage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Bolstering Rune-Circle reduces damage taken from area of effect attacks by a percentage.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="21" name="Increased Defense" icon="LesserInvisibility.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Defense by a percentage of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Defense by a percentage of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Defense by a percentage of your level.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Improved Rune of Challenge" icon="ImprovedDisciplines.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the cooldown of your Rune of Challenge by 10 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the cooldown of your Rune of Challenge by 20 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Spectral Reformation" icon="BlessedRecovery.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Remove all Spectral Wound stacks from yourself and restore Mana for each stack.

1.5 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="Support Melee (Symbology)">
        <talent index="1" name="Runic Tattoos" icon="IncantersAbsorbtion.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your base Strength by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your base Strength by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your base Strength by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your base Strength by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your base Strength by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Spectral Tattoos" icon="RemoveCurse.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your base Agility by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your base Agility by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your base Agility by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your base Agility by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your base Agility by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Runic Focus" icon="Blink.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Runic Strike and Runic Shot abilities restore Mana equal to a percentage of your Mana per 5 stat.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Runic Strike and Runic Shot abilities restore Mana equal to a percentage of your Mana per 5 stat.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Runic Strike and Runic Shot abilities restore Mana equal to a percentage of your Mana per 5 stat.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Improved Break Enchantments" icon="WispSplode.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Break Enchantments spell by 0.5 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Break Enchantments spell by 1 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the cast time of your Break Enchantments spell by 1.5 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Runic Shot" icon="NaturalWeapons.png" requires="5">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[An instant shot that deals damage Arcane damage.

8 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Spell Power to Attack Power" icon="Galvanization.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your melee and ranged Attack Power by 8% of your Spell Power.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your melee and ranged Attack Power by 16% of your Spell Power.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your melee and ranged Attack Power by 24% of your Spell Power.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your melee and ranged Attack Power by 32% of your Spell Power.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your melee and ranged Attack Power by 40% of your Spell Power.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Runic Mastery" icon="Avatar.png" requires="9">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the mana cost of your Runic Strike and Runic Shot by 50% and their cooldowns by 1 sec.

Increases the radius of your Rune-Circles by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the mana cost of your Runic Strike and Runic Shot by 100% and their cooldowns by 2 secs.

Increases the radius of your Rune-Circles by 20%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Abbreviation" icon="MindSooth.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your next Rune-Circle spell will be instant cast.

1 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Rune-Circle of Power" icon="SealOfValor.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Create a Rune-Circle of Power with a 10 yard radius at the targeted location, increasing all damage done by your party members standing inside the circle by 20%.  Lasts 20 secs.

5 second cast.
10 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="DPS Ranged (Neutralization)">
        <talent index="0" name="Execute Bonus" icon="LongShots.png" requires="1">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your critical strike chance against enemies below 20% health.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your critical strike chance against enemies below 20% health.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="1" name="On Combat Effect" icon="PrayerOfHealing.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Upon entering combat, your critical strike chance with melee and ranged attacks is increased by 5% for 15 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Upon entering combat, your critical strike chance with melee and ranged attacks is increased by 10% for 15 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Upon entering combat, your critical strike chance with melee and ranged attacks is increased by 15% for 15 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Spell Power Proc" icon="ZenArchery.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Spectral Shot, Runic Shot and Energizing Shot have a chance to increase your spell power by a percentage equal to your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Spectral Shot, Runic Shot and Energizing Shot have a chance to increase your spell power by a percentage equal to your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Spectral Shot, Runic Shot and Energizing Shot have a chance to increase your spell power by a percentage equal to your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Your Spectral Shot, Runic Shot and Energizing Shot have a chance to increase your spell power by a percentage equal to your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Your Spectral Shot, Runic Shot and Energizing Shot have a chance to increase your spell power by a percentage equal to your level.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Accuracy" icon="FocusedAim.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to hit by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Disarming Shot" icon="DisarmingShot.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Launch a charmed projectile at the target that homes in on their weapon, disarming them for 6 secs.

45 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Improved Shots" icon="Frostfire2.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Each stack of your Spectral Shot's damage over time effect increases your critical strike damage against the target.

Reduces the cooldown of your Energized Shot.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Each stack of your Spectral Shot's damage over time effect increases your critical strike damage against the target.

Reduces the cooldown of your Energized Shot.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Each stack of your Spectral Shot's damage over time effect increases your critical strike damage against the target.

Reduces the cooldown of your Energized Shot.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Each stack of your Spectral Shot's damage over time effect increases your critical strike damage against the target.

Reduces the cooldown of your Energized Shot.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Each stack of your Spectral Shot's damage over time effect increases your critical strike damage against the target.

Reduces the cooldown of your Energized Shot.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Rune of the Revenant" icon="FrostPresence.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Casts a Rune, causing your melee and normal ranged attacks to deal additional Frost damage and slow movement speed by 20% for 2 seconds.  Lasts 15 seconds or up to 6 attacks.

30 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Energized Shot" icon="ChillingBolt.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Fires a projectile infused with runic power, dealing Arcane damage to the target and energizing its Brand.

3 second cast.
30 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <notes>
        <note index="0" name="General" icon="Book_11.png"><![CDATA[Runemaster Design Ideas:

* Mixture of Death Knight, Demon Hunter, Ranger, Monk
* Available to Dwarf, Night Elf, Orc, Troll, Tauren (and maybe Gnome)
* Runic Inscriptions: The Runemaster can enchant their armor and weapons with temporary buffs (like Shaman weapon enchants). These inscriptions can also be "activated" by certain abilities
* Brands: Debuffs applied to enemy targets. Short range. Can be "energized" by certain abilities
* Circles: Apply their effects to entities standing inside the radius]]></note>
        <note index="1" name="Specifics" icon="Spy.png"><![CDATA[* Uses Mana
* Wears Leather armor
* Can use Fist Weapons, One-Handed Axes, One-Handed Maces, One-Handed Swords, Guns, Bows and Crossbows
* Can Dual Wield
* STR increases melee Attack Power by 2 per point
* AGI increases ranged Attack Power by 1 per point]]></note>
        <note index="2" name="Runic Inscriptions: Armor" icon="ArcaneResilience.png"><![CDATA[Only one Runic Inscription can be active at any time.

---
Runic Inscription: Might
Applies a Runic Inscription to your gloves, increasing your total Strength by 20%.

When activated, increases your attack speed and casting speed by 20% for 10 secs.
---
Runic Inscription: Swiftness
Applies a Runic Inscription to your boots, increasing your total Agility by 20%.

When activated, negates incoming movement impairing effects and increases your Movement Speed by 25% for 10 secs.
---
Runic Inscription: Fortification
Applies a Runic Inscription to your chest armor, increasing your maximum health by 10%.

When activated, creates a magical shield that lasts for 10 seconds, absorbing damage up to 25% of your maximum Health.
---
Runic Inscription: Wisdom
Applies a Runic Inscription to your headpiece, increasing your spell power by 40% of your Intellect.

When activated, restores 20% of your maximum Mana.
---

All Runic Inscriptions have a cast time of 10 seconds and can only be cast out of combat.]]></note>
        <note index="3" name="Runic Inscriptions: Weapons" icon="EnchantWeapon.png"><![CDATA[Only one Runic Inscription can be active at any time.

---
Runic Inscription: Impact
Applies a Runic Inscription to your melee weapon, causing your attacks to ignore 20% of the target's armor.

When activated, increases all damage done by 10% for 6 secs.
---
Runic Inscription: Precision
Applies a Runic Inscription to your ranged weapon, increasing your chance to hit by 5%.

When activated, increases your critical strike chance by 15% for 8 secs.
---

All Runic Inscriptions have a cast time of 10 seconds and can only be cast out of combat.]]></note>
        <note index="4" name="Rune-Circles" icon="NaturalPerfection.png"><![CDATA[Overlapping Rune-Circles from other Runemasters do not stack.

---
Bolstering Rune-Circle
Party members inside the Circle are slowly healed and the strength of absorb shields applied to them are increased by a percentage.

5 second cast.

---
Slowing Rune-Circle
Enemies inside the Circle have their movement, casting and attack speed slowed.

5 second cast.

---
Channeling Rune-Circle
Party members inside the Circle gain an increase in Mana restored every 5 seconds and spell pushback resistance.

5 second cast.

---
]]></note>
        <note index="5" name="Runes" icon="WordFortitude.png"><![CDATA[Rune of Backlash
Casts a Rune, causing the next enemy that attacks you in melee to be knocked down and stunned for 3 seconds.  Lasts 10 seconds.

1 minute cooldown.

---
Rune of Accumulation
Casts a Rune, causing Arcane damage in a radius around the target after it has taken a set amount of damage.  Lasts 20 seconds.

20 second cooldown.

---
Rune of Challenge
Casts a Rune, increasing your parry chance by 20% and forcing the targeted enemy to attack you for 5 secs.

50 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="6" name="Brands" icon="FireOrb.png"><![CDATA[Only one Brand can be active on the target at any time.

---
Brand of the Volcano  (Dispel type: Magic)
Causes Fire damage to nearby targets over time.

Energizing this Brand causes Fire damage in a 10 yard radius around the target.

Brand Strike against this target causes Fire damage.
---
Brand of the Vampire  (Dispel type: Curse)
Melee and ranged attackers have a chance to be healed for a percentage of the damage they deal.

Energizing this Brand reduces the target's armor for 10 secs.

Brand Strike against this target causes Shadow damage.
---
Brand of the Spellbreaker  (Dispel type: Magic)
Reduces Arcane Resistance.

Energizing this Brand dispels 1 beneficial Magic effect from the target and interrupts spellcasting for 3 secs.

Brand Strike against this target causes Arcane damage.
---

Brands have a shared cooldown of 30 secs and last for 1 minute.]]></note>
        <note index="7" name="Brands (cont.)" icon="WizardMark.png"><![CDATA[Only one Brand can be active on the target at any time.

---
Brand of the Revenant  (Dispel type: Curse)
Damaging this target has a chance to cause additional Frost damage.  This effect can occur once every 4 secs.

Energizing this Brand reduces the attack speed and casting speed of the target for 10 secs.

Brand Strike against this target causes Frost damage.
---
Brand of the Serpent  (Dispel type: Magic)
Increases damage taken from periodic effects.

Energizing this Brand reduces all healing on the target for 8 secs.

Brand Strike against this target causes Nature damage.
---

Brands have a shared cooldown of 30 secs and last for 1 minute.]]></note>
        <note index="8" name="Utility Spells" icon="StudentOfMagic.png"><![CDATA[Recitation
Activates the Runic Inscription on your equipment.

1 minute cooldown.

---
Imprison
Incapacitates an immobilized target for up to 30 seconds, as long as you keep channeling and the target does not take any damage.

30 second channel.
5 second cooldown.

---
Break Enchantments
Removes all negative Magic and Curse effects from the friendly target.

1.5 second cast.
10 second cooldown.

---
Toxin Ward
Prevents the friendly target from being afflicted by Poison and Disease effects for 20 secs.

40 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="9" name="Utility Spells (cont.)" icon="ConsumeMagic.png"><![CDATA[Spectral Dissipation
Reduces all damage taken by 25%, but a stacking Spectral Wound effect is applied to you each time you take non-periodic damage.  Lasts until cancelled.

Spectral Wound causes non-lethal Shadow damage over time and lasts for 12 seconds.

% of base Mana every 2 seconds.
3 minute cooldown.

---
Spectral Suppression
Negates damage from Spectral Wounds for 6 seconds.

45 second cooldown.

---]]></note>
        <note index="10" name="Melee Abilities" icon="FrozenRuneWeapon.png"><![CDATA[Runic Strike
Causes your next melee attack to deal additional Arcane damage.

8 second cooldown.

---
Brand Strike
Strikes the Brand on the enemy target, energizing it and dealing Arcane, Fire, Frost, Nature or Shadow damage, depending on the Brand.

30 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="11" name="Ranged Abilities" icon="TheBlackArrow.png"><![CDATA[Spectral Shot
An instant shot that deals damage and inflicts a stacking Shadow damage over time effect.

6 second cooldown.

---
Binding Shot
Fires a magical projectile, immobilizing the target for 3 secs. and slowing their Movement Speed by 40% for 6 secs.

1.5 second cast.
12 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="12" name="Runemaster's Stone" icon="StoneSkinTotem.png"><![CDATA[Runemasters receive a special trinket item that can be enchanted with Runic Inscriptions.  The activation effect of the Runic Inscription cast on the trinket item becomes its on use effect and it does not get triggered by the Recitation spell.]]></note>
    </notes>
</class>
