<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<class name="WARRIOR">
    <tree name="Arms">
        <talent index="0" name="Deflection" icon="Parry.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your Parry chance by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="1" name="Improved Overpower" icon="Overpower.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the critical strike chance of your Overpower ability by 25%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the critical strike chance of your Overpower ability by 50%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Slam" icon="DecisiveStrike.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Slams the opponent, causing weapon damage plus 4.

25 Rage. 1.5 second cast.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="3" name="Improved Slam" icon="ImpSlam.png" requires="2">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Slam ability by 25% and reduces the Rage cost by 2.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Slam ability by 50% and reduces the Rage cost by 4.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Slam ability by 75% and reduces the Rage cost by 7.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Slam ability by 100% and reduces the Rage cost by 10.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Improved Battle Stance" icon="OffensiveStance.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[While in Battle Stance, your chance to hit is increased by 1% and your Heroic Strike, Mortal Strike, Slam and Cleave hits have an 11% chance to generate 5 Rage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[While in Battle Stance, your chance to hit is increased by 2% and your Heroic Strike, Mortal Strike, Slam and Cleave hits have a 22% chance to generate 5 Rage.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[While in Battle Stance, your chance to hit is increased by 3% and your Heroic Strike, Mortal Strike, Slam and Cleave hits have a 33% chance to generate 5 Rage.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Improved Heroic Strike" icon="Ambush.png" requires="1">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Heroic Strike hits increase the critical strike chance of your next damaging ability by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Heroic Strike hits increase the critical strike chance of your next damaging ability by 17%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Heroic Strike hits increase the critical strike chance of your next damaging ability by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Tactical Mastery" icon="EnchantArmor.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[You retain up to 10 of your rage points when you change stances.

Increases the range of your Charge, Intervene and Intercept abilities by 2 yards.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[You retain up to 20 of your rage points when you change stances.

Increases the range of your Charge, Intervene and Intercept abilities by 4 yards.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[You retain up to 30 of your rage points when you change stances.

Increases the range of your Charge, Intervene and Intercept abilities by 6 yards.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Weapon Master" icon="ArmsWeapon.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you immunity to Disarm effects and increases the rate at which you learn Weapon Skill by 100%.

Increases your critical strike chance with melee attacks by 50% of your Parry chance.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Momentum" icon="DevastatingBlows.png" requires="2">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to build up Momentum, reducing the cast time of your next Slam by 0.1 secs. per stack of Momentum.  Stacks up to 15 times and lasts 20 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to build up Momentum, reducing the cast time of your next Slam by 0.2 secs. per stack of Momentum.  Stacks up to 10 times and lasts 20 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to build up Momentum, reducing the cast time of your next Slam by 0.3 secs. per stack of Momentum.  Stacks up to 5 times and lasts 20 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to build up Momentum, reducing the cast time of your next Slam by 0.4 secs. per stack of Momentum.  Stacks up to 4 times and lasts 20 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to build up Momentum, reducing the cast time of your next Slam by 0.5 secs. per stack of Momentum.  Stacks up to 3 times and lasts 20 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Improved Hamstring" icon="Shockwave.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your Charge and Intercept abilities a 50% chance to make your next Hamstring immobilize its target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your Charge and Intercept abilities a 100% chance to make your next Hamstring immobilize its target for 3 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="12" name="Spell Parry" icon="Spellparry.jpg">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you the ability to parry direct damage spells, if cast from more than 15 yds away, reducing the damage by up to 150% of your total Strength.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you the ability to parry direct damage spells, if cast from more than 15 yds away, reducing the damage by up to 300% of your total Strength.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Impale" icon="SearingArrow.png" requires="5">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the critical strike damage bonus of your abilities by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the critical strike damage bonus of your abilities by 10%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Focused Assault" icon="UnrelentingAssault.png" requires="10">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to increase your attack speed by 1%, up to a maximum of 5%.  Lasts 6 secs. but expires if you lose focus on the target.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to increase your attack speed by 1%, up to a maximum of 10%.  Lasts 6 secs. but expires if you lose focus on the target.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives your melee attacks a chance to increase your attack speed by 1%, up to a maximum of 15%.  Lasts 6 secs. but expires if you lose focus on the target.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="15" name="Two-Handed Weapon Specialization" icon="2Hand.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Grants you a passive effect depending on the base attack speed of your equipped two-handed weapon.

Weapons with an attack speed of 3.0 and faster give your damaging ability hits a 3% chance to grant you an extra attack.

Weapons with an attack speed slower than 3.0 increase Rage generation from dealing damage by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Grants you a passive effect depending on the base attack speed of your equipped two-handed weapon.

Weapons with an attack speed of 3.0 and faster give your damaging ability hits a 6% chance to grant you an extra attack.

Weapons with an attack speed slower than 3.0 increase Rage generation from dealing damage by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Grants you a passive effect depending on the base attack speed of your equipped two-handed weapon.

Weapons with an attack speed of 3.0 and faster give your damaging ability hits a 9% chance to grant you an extra attack.

Weapons with an attack speed slower than 3.0 increase Rage generation from dealing damage by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Grants you a passive effect depending on the base attack speed of your equipped two-handed weapon.

Weapons with an attack speed of 3.0 and faster give your damaging ability hits a 12% chance to grant you an extra attack.

Weapons with an attack speed slower than 3.0 increase Rage generation from dealing damage by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Grants you a passive effect depending on the base attack speed of your equipped two-handed weapon.

Weapons with an attack speed of 3.0 and faster give your damaging ability hits a 15% chance to grant you an extra attack.

Weapons with an attack speed slower than 3.0 increase Rage generation from dealing damage by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Poleaxe Specialization" icon="Polearm.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with Axes and Polearms by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with Axes and Polearms by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with Axes and Polearms by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with Axes and Polearms by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with Axes and Polearms by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Sweeping Strikes" icon="SliceDice.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your next 5 melee attacks strike an additional nearby opponent.

30 Rage.  30 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Mace Specialization" icon="Mace.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your melee attacks with a Mace ignore 4% of the target's armor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your melee attacks with a Mace ignore 8% of the target's armor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your melee attacks with a Mace ignore 12% of the target's armor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Your melee attacks with a Mace ignore 16% of the target's armor.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Your melee attacks with a Mace ignore 20% of the target's armor.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="19" name="Sword Specialization" icon="Sword.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your attack speed and chance to parry with Swords by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your attack speed and chance to parry with Swords by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your attack speed and chance to parry with Swords by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your attack speed and chance to parry with Swords by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your attack speed and chance to parry with Swords by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="21" name="Weapon Expertise" icon="WeaponMaster.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your Weapon Skill with all weapons by 2.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your Weapon Skill with all weapons by 4.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your Weapon Skill with all weapons by 6.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Mortal Strike (Rank 1)" icon="SavageBlow.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[A vicious strike that deals weapon damage plus 85 and wounds the target, reducing the effectiveness of any healing by 50% for 10 sec.

30 Rage.  6 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="Fury">
        <talent index="1" name="Intimidating Presence" icon="ShamanRage.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces the target's chance to resist your Taunt and Challenging Shout abilities by 1%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Intimidating Shout ability by 12 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces the target's chance to resist your Taunt and Challenging Shout abilities by 2%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Intimidating Shout ability by 24 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces the target's chance to resist your Taunt and Challenging Shout abilities by 3%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Intimidating Shout ability by 36 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces the target's chance to resist your Taunt and Challenging Shout abilities by 4%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Intimidating Shout ability by 48 seconds.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces the target's chance to resist your Taunt and Challenging Shout abilities by 5%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Intimidating Shout ability by 60 seconds.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Booming Voice" icon="Purge.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the area of effect and duration of your Battle Shout, Demoralizing Shout and Disrupting Shout's slowing effect by 10%.

Increases the melee attack power bonus of your Battle Shout by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the area of effect and duration of your Battle Shout, Demoralizing Shout and Disrupting Shout's slowing effect by 20%.

Increases the melee attack power bonus of your Battle Shout by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases the area of effect and duration of your Battle Shout, Demoralizing Shout and Disrupting Shout's slowing effect by 30%.

Increases the melee attack power bonus of your Battle Shout by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases the area of effect and duration of your Battle Shout, Demoralizing Shout and Disrupting Shout's slowing effect by 40%.

Increases the melee attack power bonus of your Battle Shout by 20%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases the area of effect and duration of your Battle Shout, Demoralizing Shout and Disrupting Shout's slowing effect by 50%.

Increases the melee attack power bonus of your Battle Shout by 25%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Blood Craze" icon="SummonImp.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Regenerates 2% of your total Health over 6 sec after being the victim of a critical strike.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Regenerates 4% of your total Health over 6 sec after being the victim of a critical strike.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Regenerates 6% of your total Health over 6 sec after being the victim of a critical strike.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="5" name="Implacable" icon="FleetFooted.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your movement speed by 4%.

Gives you a 5% chance to reset the cooldown of your Intercept and Intervene abilities after being hit with a movement impairing effect.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your movement speed by 8%.

Gives you a 10% chance to reset the cooldown of your Intercept and Intervene abilities after being hit with a movement impairing effect.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Blood Haze" icon="04_1.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from critical strikes by 10% when your Health is below 35%.

Increases the damage done by your Bleed effects by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from critical strikes by 15% when your Health is below 35%.

Increases the damage done by your Bleed effects by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces damage taken from critical strikes by 20% when your Health is below 35%.

Increases the damage done by your Bleed effects by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Focused Rage" icon="FocusedRage.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Bloodrage ability increases your melee attack power by 30% of your level while active.

Your Berserker Rage ability will generate 2 Rage when used.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Bloodrage ability increases your melee attack power by 60% of your level while active.

Your Berserker Rage ability will generate 4 Rage when used.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Your Bloodrage ability increases your melee attack power by 90% of your level while active.

Your Berserker Rage ability will generate 6 Rage when used.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Your Bloodrage ability increases your melee attack power by 120% of your level while active.

Your Berserker Rage ability will generate 8 Rage when used.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Your Bloodrage ability increases your melee attack power by 150% of your level while active.

Your Berserker Rage ability will generate 10 Rage when used.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Furious Throw" icon="Heroism.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Throws your off-hand weapon at the enemy, dealing weapon damage, causing them bleed for 60 damage over 12 seconds and slowing their movement speed by 40% for the duration.

1 second cast.
15 Rage.  1 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Cruelty" icon="Eviscerate.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with melee weapons by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with melee weapons by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with melee weapons by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with melee weapons by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to get a critical strike with melee weapons by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="12" name="Enrage" icon="UnholyFrenzy.png" requires="4">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 10% melee damage bonus for 12 sec up to a maximum of 6 swings after being the victim of a critical strike.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 20% melee damage bonus for 12 sec up to a maximum of 6 swings after being the victim of a critical strike.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="13" name="Improved Execute" icon="Execute.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Restores 10 Rage and 5% of your total Health over 12 seconds after using Execute.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 30 secs.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Restores 20 Rage and 10% of your total Health over 12 seconds after using Execute.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 30 secs.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="15" name="Dual Wield Specialization" icon="DualWield.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your Heroic Strike, Overpower, Slam, Execute, Whirlwind, Cleave and Bloodthirst hits a 10% chance to deal extra damage equal to the damage per second of your off-hand weapon.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your Heroic Strike, Overpower, Slam, Execute, Whirlwind, Cleave and Bloodthirst hits a 20% chance to deal extra damage equal to the damage per second of your off-hand weapon.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives your Heroic Strike, Overpower, Slam, Execute, Whirlwind, Cleave and Bloodthirst hits a 30% chance to deal extra damage equal to the damage per second of your off-hand weapon.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives your Heroic Strike, Overpower, Slam, Execute, Whirlwind, Cleave and Bloodthirst hits a 40% chance to deal extra damage equal to the damage per second of your off-hand weapon.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives your Heroic Strike, Overpower, Slam, Execute, Whirlwind, Cleave and Bloodthirst hits a 50% chance to deal extra damage equal to the damage per second of your off-hand weapon.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Seethe" icon="IntensifyRage.png" requires="12">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that causes the next incoming attack to Enrage you and deal 50% of its damage over 6 seconds instead.  This effect is refreshed once you haven't been damaged for at least 60 secs.

Reduces damage taken from periodic effects by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that causes the next incoming attack to Enrage you and deal 50% of its damage over 6 seconds instead.  This effect is refreshed once you haven't been damaged for at least 40 secs.

Reduces damage taken from periodic effects by 10%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives you a passive effect that causes the next incoming attack to Enrage you and deal 50% of its damage over 6 seconds instead.  This effect is refreshed once you haven't been damaged for at least 20 secs.

Reduces damage taken from periodic effects by 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Mortal Wounds" icon="CriticalStrike.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Furious Throw bleed effect reduces the effectiveness of any healing on the target by 10%.

Your Rend ability reduces the effectiveness of any healing on the target by 2% per application.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Furious Throw bleed effect reduces the effectiveness of any healing on the target by 20%.

Your Rend ability reduces the effectiveness of any healing on the target by 4% per application.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Improved Berserker Stance" icon="Avatar.png" requires="6">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[While in Berserker Stance, your attack power is increased by 50% of your level, and your attack speed is increased by an additional 10% when your Health is below 35%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[While in Berserker Stance, your attack power is increased by 100% of your level, and your attack speed is increased by an additional 15% when your Health is below 35%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[While in Berserker Stance, your attack power is increased by 150% of your level, and your attack speed is increased by an additional 20% when your Health is below 35%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="19" name="Death Wish" icon="DeathPact.png" requires="18">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[When activated, increases your physical damage by 20% and makes you immune to Fear and Incapacitate effects, but increases the chance to be critically hit by 10%.  Lasts 20 sec.

10 Rage.  3 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="22" name="Reaper" icon="FlameBlades.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Cleave ability by 50%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Whirlwind ability by 3 seconds.

Increases the critical strike chance of your Execute ability by 5%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the bonus damage of your Cleave ability by 100%.

Reduces the cooldown of your Whirlwind ability by 6 seconds.

Increases the critical strike chance of your Execute ability by 10%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Bloodthirst (Rank 1)" icon="BloodLust.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Instantly attack the target causing damage equal to 33% of your attack power plus 65, and restoring 50 Health if the target is bleeding.

25 Rage.  6 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <tree name="Protection">
        <talent index="0" name="Improved Defensive Stance" icon="DefensiveStance.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases the damage reduction of your Defensive Stance by an additional 10% when you are immobilized.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases the damage reduction of your Defensive Stance by an additional 20% when you are immobilized.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="1" name="Shield Specialization" icon="Shield.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 20% chance to generate 1 Rage when a block occurs.

Increases your chance to block attacks with a shield by 1%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 40% chance to generate 1 Rage when a block occurs.

Increases your chance to block attacks with a shield by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Gives you a 60% chance to generate 1 Rage when a block occurs.

Increases your chance to block attacks with a shield by 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Gives you a 80% chance to generate 1 Rage when a block occurs.

Increases your chance to block attacks with a shield by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Gives you a 100% chance to generate 1 Rage when a block occurs.

Increases your chance to block attacks with a shield by 5%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="2" name="Iron Will" icon="MageArmor.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Charm, Disorient and Sleep effects by an additional 3%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Charm, Disorient and Sleep effects by an additional 6%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Charm, Disorient and Sleep effects by an additional 9%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Charm, Disorient and Sleep effects by an additional 12%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your chance to resist Stun, Charm, Disorient and Sleep effects by an additional 15%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="4" name="Anticipation" icon="MirrorImage.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Grants the damage reduction of Defensive Stance for 0.5 seconds after changing out of it.

Increases your Defense skill by 10% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Grants the damage reduction of Defensive Stance for 1.0 seconds after changing out of it.

Increases your Defense skill by 20% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Grants the damage reduction of Defensive Stance for 1.5 seconds after changing out of it.

Increases your Defense skill by 30% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Grants the damage reduction of Defensive Stance for 2.0 seconds after changing out of it.

Increases your Defense skill by 40% of your level.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Grants the damage reduction of Defensive Stance for 2.5 seconds after changing out of it.

Increases your Defense skill by 50% of your level.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="6" name="Defender's Resolve" icon="ImprovedDisciplines.png" requires="2">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives you a 25% chance to negate a Charm, Disorient or Sleep effect, reducing your movement speed by 25% and your chance to hit by 50% for 6 seconds instead.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives you a 50% chance to negate a Charm, Disorient or Sleep effect, reducing your movement speed by 25% and your chance to hit by 50% for 6 seconds instead.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="7" name="Vendetta" icon="Vendetta.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Killing a target that yields honor or experience finishes the cooldown of all your abilities with a base cooldown time equal to or faster than 30 secs.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 60 secs.

Your Revenge hits reduce the remaining cooldown of your Protection abilities by 0.5 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Killing a target that yields honor or experience finishes the cooldown of all your abilities with a base cooldown time equal to or faster than 45 secs.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 60 secs.

Your Revenge hits reduce the remaining cooldown of your Protection abilities by 1 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Killing a target that yields honor or experience finishes the cooldown of all your abilities with a base cooldown time equal to or faster than 60 secs.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 60 secs.

Your Revenge hits reduce the remaining cooldown of your Protection abilities by 2 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="8" name="Shield Slam (Rank 1)" icon="FireArmor.png" requires="9">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Slam the target with your shield, causing 130 to 140 damage, plus your total Strength.  Causes a high amount of threat.

20 Rage.  6 second cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="9" name="Improved Shield Block" icon="Defend.png" requires="1">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Your Shield Block ability increases your block strength by 25% while active.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Your Shield Block ability increases your block strength by 50% while active.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="10" name="Disrupting Shout" icon="RallyingCry.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Interrupts the target for 3 seconds and dazing all enemies within 10 yards for 6 seconds.

30 Rage.  3 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="11" name="Devastator" icon="Devastate.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Generates 1 Rage when you attack targets with Physical damage absorbing shields.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 6 seconds.

Your Shield Bash and Disrupting Shout abilities silence their targets for 1 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Generates 2 Rage when you attack targets with Physical damage absorbing shields.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 6 seconds.

Your Shield Bash and Disrupting Shout abilities silence their targets for 1.5 sec.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Generates 3 Rage when you attack targets with Physical damage absorbing shields.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 6 seconds.

Your Shield Bash and Disrupting Shout abilities silence their targets for 2 sec.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="12" name="One-Handed Weapon Specialization" icon="1Hand.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your damage and threat caused with One-Handed Melee weapons by 2%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your damage and threat caused with One-Handed Melee weapons by 4%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your damage and threat caused with One-Handed Melee weapons by 6%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your damage and threat caused with One-Handed Melee weapons by 8%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your damage and threat caused with One-Handed Melee weapons by 10%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="14" name="Toughness" icon="Toughness.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Increases your total Stamina by 1% and your Strength by 2% of your Stamina.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Increases your total Stamina by 2% and your Strength by 4% of your Stamina.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Increases your total Stamina by 3% and your Strength by 6% of your Stamina.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Increases your total Stamina by 4% and your Strength by 8% of your Stamina.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Increases your total Stamina by 5% and your Strength by 10% of your Stamina.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="16" name="Vanguard" icon="InnerRage.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Generates 2 Rage when you parry, dodge or resist an attack or ability.

Increases your damage done by 2% for each enemy within 10 yds of you.  Stacks up to 5 times.

Reduces the cooldown of your Challenging Shout ability by 2 minutes.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Generates 5 Rage when you parry, dodge or resist an attack or ability.

Increases your damage done by 2% for each enemy within 10 yds of you.  Stacks up to 10 times.

Reduces the cooldown of your Challenging Shout ability by 4 minutes.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="17" name="Shield Mastery" icon="ShieldMastery.png" requires="9">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Gives your Shield Bash, Shield Slam and Intervene abilities a 50% chance to give you charge of Shield Block.

Increases the amount of damage absorbed by your shield by 15%.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Gives your Shield Bash, Shield Slam and Intervene abilities a 100% chance to give you charge of Shield Block.

Increases the amount of damage absorbed by your shield by 30%.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="18" name="Shockwave (Rank 1)" icon="Shockwave_1.png">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Sends a wave of force in front of the warrior, causing damage equal to your total Strength plus 60 and stunning all enemy targets within 10 yards in a frontal cone for 3 sec.

50 Rage.  1 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="21" name="Hold the Line" icon="Vigilance.png" requires="17">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces all damage taken by 10% for 6 secs. when your Health drops below 20%.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 5 minutes.]]></rank>
            <rank index="2"><![CDATA[Reduces all damage taken by 15% for 6 secs. when your Health drops below 20%.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 5 minutes.]]></rank>
            <rank index="3"><![CDATA[Reduces all damage taken by 20% for 6 secs. when your Health drops below 20%.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 5 minutes.]]></rank>
            <rank index="4"><![CDATA[Reduces all damage taken by 25% for 6 secs. when your Health drops below 20%.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 5 minutes.]]></rank>
            <rank index="5"><![CDATA[Reduces all damage taken by 30% for 6 secs. when your Health drops below 20%.  This effect cannot occur more than once every 5 minutes.]]></rank>
        </talent>
        <talent index="25" name="Shield Wall" icon="ShieldWall.png" requires="21">
            <rank index="1"><![CDATA[Reduces all non-periodic damage taken by 30% for 6 sec.

5 minute cooldown.]]></rank>
        </talent>
    </tree>
    <notes>
        <note index="0" name="General" icon="Book_11.png"><![CDATA[Thunder Clap - REMOVED

Slam - Now an Arms talent.

Shield Wall - Now a Protection talent.

Rend - Now a Fury skill and can stack up to 5 times.

Sunder Armor - Armor reducing effect lowered.

Challenging Shout - Cooldown lowered to 5 minutes, duration reduced to 3 seconds.

Whirlwind - Cooldown increased to 15 secs.]]></note>
        <note index="1" name="Miscellaneous" icon="Spy.png"><![CDATA[Rend only has 1 debuff slot (like Sunder Armor, one stack per mob)]]></note>
        <note index="10" name="(NEW) Intervene" icon="VictoryRush.png"><![CDATA[Run at high speed towards a party member, intercepting the next melee or ranged attack made against them.

10 Rage. 30 second cooldown.]]></note>
        <note index="12" name="(NEW) Second Wind" icon="Harass.png"><![CDATA[Break free from Stun, Incapacitate and Movement Impairing effects, and regenerate 50% of your total Health over 30 secs.

30 minute cooldown]]></note>
    </notes>
</class>
